[
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68]?",
      "correctAnswer": "64",
      "options": [
        "63",
        "64",
        "65",
        "66"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69]?",
      "correctAnswer": "65",
      "options": [
        "64",
        "65",
        "66",
        "67"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70]?",
      "correctAnswer": "66",
      "options": [
        "65",
        "66",
        "67",
        "68"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71]?",
      "correctAnswer": "67",
      "options": [
        "66",
        "67",
        "68",
        "69"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72]?",
      "correctAnswer": "68",
      "options": [
        "67",
        "68",
        "69",
        "70"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73]?",
      "correctAnswer": "69",
      "options": [
        "68",
        "69",
        "70",
        "71"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74]?",
      "correctAnswer": "70",
      "options": [
        "69",
        "70",
        "71",
        "72"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75]?",
      "correctAnswer": "71",
      "options": [
        "70",
        "71",
        "72",
        "73"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76]?",
      "correctAnswer": "72",
      "options": [
        "71",
        "72",
        "73",
        "74"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these numbers:<br> [70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77]?",
      "correctAnswer": "73",
      "options": [
        "72",
        "73",
        "74",
        "75"
      ]
    }
]